Hello viewers, the printed synthetic results are there
and according to Mukesh, if you look at it,
operationally, there is a
slight pressure on the quality of the serious search from the numbers,
provisioning has increased, but the special thing is that
from next year, there will be a
slight increase in Morgan Stanley, this serial will be seen
related to it and after that, both have
seen a good increase,
according to that, so let me show you one by one,
see this in this way, subscribe five times,
one is 525 in that, the flexible and friends,
this is a little result, like Naira, which is under
pressure on good quality, one should go ahead and
see their feedback, or that is why they have
maintained the underperform rating,
Laxmi 434, on that, the least
positive on the tricks, this Pimple and
Laxman have increased slightly from 500 to
520, the most that
from this gang, Nindiya 610 and the least
hair tips were missed chances of that, apart from this,
if you see, there were results of HDFC Life as well
and there is a CBSE report on it, the
purchase light has been kept off except for 40 that house
rs.730 has been increased to rs.486 yesterday
because of this type of going there it is quite good
seeing them with you pressure
persistence stairs with Dixit is bad
one now it is visible below this
previous report on next Ambuja Cement and
here as a state from its side
that if you look at all 12 meters then the
results on bowling are quite good
and the updating is maintained it has
increased from 176 to 194 Morgan Stanley has
also released a report on the price of give them on time
and has maintained the rating apart from this
you will get to
see a lot of avatars on the volume of cigarettes due to people subscribing to anything and there is
hotel business there if you
look at hotel business for you in the morning then even in such a situation the
income of the company is less than 5 years and half a
minute but a small
plate Bluetooth is also visible on ITC
that there is a problem